

Address : Blk 331 Woodlands Ave 1 #11-409 S (730 331)

Gender : Female Nationality : Singaporean

Contact Nos : +65 8125 9555 (Mobile)
E-mail : hilowvalerie@yahoo.com.sq

EDUCATION

Sep 2006 to Apr 2008 : Bachelor of Commerce – Murdoch University

(Majors in Management & Minor Marketing Management)

Sep 2005 to Aug 2006 : SMa School of Management

Diploma in Business Administration

(Major in Management)

Feb 2004 to Sep 2004 : Bunka Language School

Japanese Elementary (JPT)

CAREER SUMMARY

With over 10 years of customer service experiences in Banking & Financial, Media, and Telecommunication industries.

Currently, having more than 7 years working experiences in asset management environment as a Fund Accountant and also been responsible for an important role of the team as a Client Service Representative (CSR). As a CSR, my role includes in handling client's day to day queries and requests on top of daily fund accounting operational tasks.

Be the main in-charge of billing function of the team, my role is required me to work closely with internal colleagues to ensure all the reports and invoices were produced accurately to our client. Liaising and follow-up with relevant parties to ensure any billing related issues or requests being addressed immediately.

On top of CSR and Billing roles, I also responsible in handling Tax queries which involve advising client on how to fill the form and follow-up with client on submission tax reclaim forms in any event. I will need to prepare and provide the data files or income reports base on client's requests.

Looking at my prior job, working as a Customer Service Executive in MediaCorp leading subscription team in circulation department, to train, direct and motivate staffs. Having abilities to manage and coordinate active plans for daily operation of subscription team. Establish work priorities and assist staffs with problem resolution. Also part of Project team member for implementation of the new subscriber system and online subscription website to support the business and improve customer service.

CONTRACT EMPLOYMENT

Personal Assistant to Director AIA - Rayner Lee & Associate Sep 2016 – Dec 2016 (4mths contract)

Key Responsibilities:

Secretarial Support

- Liaising with internal & external clients.
- Calendar Management.
- Maintaining monthly birthday list & cake ordering matters.
- Petty cash management & Account management contribution.
- Home management.
- Travel & other arrangements.
- Maintain Director's personal social media account.
- Maintain proper filing systems.
- Ad-hoc responsibilities.

Account & Finance Management

- Review monthly AIA financial Statements, perform monthly banking & finance tracking duties.
- Liaising with Accounting team with IRAS & GST matters.
- Payroll administration & CPF contribution.
- Petty cash management & Account management contribution.

Staffs Management

- On-boarding of new staffs
- General; HR management, including medical leaves, annual leaves, reimbursements, etc.

Business Management

- Liaising with AIA management.
- Handling service & recovery matters.

Compliance Management

- Financial Health Review (FHR)
- Writing minutes for weekly leaders meeting / group agency meeting (average 3 hours duration meeting minutes per session).
- ICM management includes for coaching, meeting attendance/minutes, FHR assignments.

Investment Management

- Liaising with Business partnership
- Handling & manage overseas ventures related stuffs.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Fund Accountant
Bank of New York Mellon
Feb 2009 – Aug 2016 (7 ½ yrs)

Key Responsibilities:

Fund Accounting

- > Perform Cash/FM Reconciliation for daily and monthly accounts.
- > Review daily funds and accounting reports.
- > Performing the mid month and month end reporting and analysis reports.
- > Prepare data files daily and perform investigation upon any issues arise.
- Ensure all NAV's/reports and other deliverables are produced in accordance to agreed service level standards.

Client Serving duties

- Maintaining a strong and good relationship with client. Handle daily client queries through emails or phones. Monitor closely to the mailboxes and response to the client queries promptly. Resolving any queries like billing issues, fees related queries, accounting enquiries, new account set up matters, any client reporting requests and etc.
- > Analyze the fund instructions issued by client and feedback to client if there is any issues related to the instruction.
- Daily keep a lookup for any incoming faxes in the inbox and distribute the instructions to the respective parties to ensure all instructions been processed accordingly and assist the FA if they have any queries related to the instructions.
- > Liaising with Fund Manager and Custody Representative to ensure smooth processing.

Billing

- > Be in charge of billing function includes preparing and following up closely with the relevant parties. This is to ensure reports are provided accurately to client and internal colleagues.
- Review any billing reporting and analysis reports
- Having ability to troubleshoot and resolve any issues related to billing and fees such as follow-up Business Client Solution team/oversea billing team to resolve the new account billing issues and etc.
- Monitoring any fee instructions received and informing the billing to process and drop the accrual accordingly.
- Handling Relationship Manager's queries about billing status such as aging report, write off, fee issue, billing close account or new account created and etc.

Fund Administration

- Analyze the fund operational memo and feedback to client if there is any issues related to the contract.
- > Handling fund related payments.
- > Prepare any fund payment template and liaising with various parties to set up treasury edge for the new account set up.
- > Teaching and guide the fund admin teammates how to process trade orders, prepare payments, do monthly fund statement, verification process, monitoring and answering any fund related emails and etc.

Workflow Improvement responsibilities

- > Pioneer to run new funds. Subsequently, pass on to newbie to run the funds.
- Teach and guide the newbie how to run the daily/monthly funds, month end work process and other work tasks.
- > Prepare and written all Client Specific Procedures/Standard Operation Procedures to have a proper guidelines to improve current workflows such as the following reports;
 - -Daily Accounts Processing
 - -Feeder Fund Portfolio Procedures
 - -Billing Expense Process
 - -MAS Derivative Processing
 - -Daily Price Check Procedure
 - -Others guidelines reports
- > Assist with ad-hoc projects.

System Testing/Macro Updates duties

- > Handling reports/system testing to improvise the current working process
- Liaising with IT with regards to macros and do testing of the macro to update new funds or any new client requests.

Achievement:

- Responsible for an important role in the team as a client servicing representative.
- Main in-charge of the billing function

Customer Service Exceutive MediaCorp Pte Ltd (Publishing) Feb 2005 – Jan 2009 (4 yrs)

Key Responsibilities:

- Provide customer service to clients; Investigate into customers' complaints and resolve problems by recommending possible actions and solutions.
- > Work out sampling proposal to island wide distribution.
- > Handle new and existing corporate account to various corporations.
- > Monitor stock levels, usage and generate forecast of requirements
- > Perform inventory control and management.
- > Generate and coordination of quotations.
- > Responsible for establishing monitoring reports to help monitor both system and/or personnel performance levels, customer survey evaluation and analysis reports.
- Attending department leaders monthly meeting to present my team sales subscriptions statics.
- > Prepare weekly and monthly report to Vice President.

Other Duties:

- > Coordinate and support major sales & marketing activities
- > Handle new subscription system implementation such written new system specification requirements, system testing, monitoring system workability and etc.

Achievement:

- Supervisory role leading a team of subscription division.
- Project team member for subscription system implementation.

SingTel Mobile Pte Ltd - Customer Service Officer Jun 2000 – Jan 2005 (4 ½ yrs)

Key Responsibilities:

- > Assist Manager to prepare daily & monthly reports on customer's feedback /mobile services/ rejects.
- > Answering customer enquiries & follow up on queries.
- > Handing corporate accounts and updating of corporate individual scheme rate.
- > Replying daily email enquiries. On top of that, further investigate are require & to resolve as soon as possible.
- > Checking mobile airtime & subscription, doing calculate & raising adjustment.
- > Data Entry of Subscriber's information to the database system.
- > Training to new & existing junior staff.
- Distribute work to staffs for processing.

S.T.E Engineering Pte Ltd - Admin Assistant Jan 1999 – May 2000 (1 1/2years)

Key Responsibilities:

- > Perform administrative functions including office maintenance and operations, travel arrangements, and handling of correspondence.
- Assist Supervisor in Data Entry & Filing.
- > Assist Supervisor in preparing monthly statistics reports

- > Provide Phone Support to Customers on any enquires.
- > Preparing invoices and Documents.
- > Assist in other ad-hoc projects, assignments & activities.

COMPUTER SKILLS

Competent in Microsoft Words, Excel, Microsoft Outlook, PowerPoint etc. Typing Speed: 30 words per minutes

STRENGTH:

Willing to learn new things to keep improving myself Independent and able to take on multiple assignments under pressure Love to accept any challenges and work in a dynamic environment

LANGUAGE

Bilingual in speaking & writing in English, Mandarin